<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Policies on Policies | Flutter Bounty Hunters</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/</link><description>Recent content in Policies on Policies | Flutter Bounty Hunters</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding Your Project to Our Portfolio</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/adding-your-project-to-our-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/adding-your-project-to-our-portfolio/</guid><description>Do you have an open source Flutter or Dart package? Would you like for companies to fund further development? Would your package make sense within the Flutter Bounty Hunters portfolio? If so, let’s talk!
The Flutter Bounty Hunters is a remote team of Flutter and Dart developers who work exclusively on open source packages. We find companies that need infrastructure tools, and then we work with those companies to setup funding, and build what they need.</description></item><item><title>Bounty Hunter Expectations</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/bounty-hunter-expectations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/bounty-hunter-expectations/</guid><description>The Flutter Bounty Hunters aim to be as flexible with its team, as possible. The team is remote, allowing developers to work from any location in the world, at times, and in ways that are preferred by the developer. Each Bounty Hunter is invited to work on projects as they become available. Bounty Hunters won&amp;rsquo;t be forced to work on projects that don&amp;rsquo;t interest them.
With great flexibility comes great responsibility.</description></item><item><title>Bounty Hunter Rates</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/bounty-hunter-rates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/bounty-hunter-rates/</guid><description>Flutter Bounty Hunters log development hours against specific tickets. Every ticket is categorized by complexity, and hourly rates are determined by those categories.
Bounty Hunters are compensated based on the following rates:
Junior Development: $60 / hour Senior Development: $100 / hour Specialist Development: $125 / hour Tech Leadership: $150 / hour</description></item><item><title>Client Rates</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/client-rates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/client-rates/</guid><description>Flutter Bounty Hunters log development hours against specific tickets. Every ticket is categorized by complexity, and hourly rates are determined by those categories.
Clients are charged based on the following rates:
Junior Development: $85 / hour Senior Development: $125 / hour Specialist Development: $150 / hour Tech Leadership: $200 / hour</description></item><item><title>How Bounty Hunters Work</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/how-bounty-hunters-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/how-bounty-hunters-work/</guid><description>The Flutter Bounty Hunters connect experienced developers with corporate clients to produce high quality open source tools for the Flutter and Dart ecosystems.
Bounty Hunters are contractors All Flutter Bounty Hunters are contractors. Bounty Hunters work from their desired locations, at desired times, using their own equipment.
Work is sporadic Bounty Hunter work becomes available as companies choose to fund development milestones. Therefore, Bounty Hunters have no guarantee of any particular work volume, or schedule.</description></item><item><title>How to become a Flutter Bounty Hunter</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/how-to-become-a-bounty-hunter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/how-to-become-a-bounty-hunter/</guid><description>So, you want to become a Flutter Bounty Hunter? Great!
Please review Who should become a Flutter Bounty Hunter, to ensure that you have the appropriate experience. Please review Bounty Hunter Expectations, to ensure that you&amp;rsquo;re up for the challenge. Please review How the Flutter Bounty Hunters work, to ensure that you know what you&amp;rsquo;re signing up for. How to join If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to join the Flutter Bounty Hunters, please send an application.</description></item><item><title>How to fund a milestone</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/fund-milestone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/fund-milestone/</guid><description>A milestone is an individual funding and development event for the Flutter Bounty Hunters.
The Flutter Bounty Hunters don’t fund individual development tickets, because individual tickets are too small to be worth the coordination with funding companies. Instead, the Flutter Bounty Hunters define broader development goals, called milestones. A milestone might correspond to any number of development tickets.
Here are some example milestones:
Add support for mobile text entry Add undo/redo support to the document editor Add support for more video filters Fix bugs in the mobile text field Crowdfunding A milestone might include any number of funding companies.</description></item><item><title>What is a Proof-of-Concept</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/proof-of-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/proof-of-concept/</guid><description>A Flutter Bounty Hunters Proof-of-Concept project is a new project that’s searching for funding.
From time to time the Flutter Bounty Hunters come up with ideas for new projects without any request from funding companies. Rather than pitch companies on the idea of a new project, we invest the time to build a prototype that demonstrates the project concept. This prototype demonstrates that the Flutter Bounty Hunters are capable of building the new project, and also demonstrates why we think the project is valuable.</description></item><item><title>Who should become a Flutter Bounty Hunter?</title><link>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/who-should-become-a-bounty-hunter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://policies.flutterbountyhunters.com/who-should-become-a-bounty-hunter/</guid><description>The Flutter Bounty Hunters are an elite team of Flutter and Dart developers who are working to build the future of the Flutter and Dart ecosystems. We work on behalf of paying clients, who need infrastructure tools, to ship their products.
A strong candidate for the Flutter Bounty Hunters is experienced, accomplished, and committed.
Experience Some lessons are only learned through experience. To ensure the success of our projects, a Flutter Bounty Hunter should have at least a year of professional development experience with Flutter or Dart, and multiple years of development experience, in general.</description></item></channel></rss>